Guide to the National Law Center records, 1865-2005 RG0014
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Law alumni photographs, 1921-1989; RG0014 Series 13; 7.5 Linear feet (Box 9, Box 8, Box 7, Box 6, Box 13, Box 12, Box 11, Box 10, Box 15, Box 14, Box 1, Box 2, Box 3, Box 4, Box 5)
  - Senior Reception, Lawyers' Club, 04/15/1972 (Box 5, Folder 76.6)
    Mr and Mrs. Dubaff, Mr. and Mrs. Pettinger Philip, Herrick
  - Senior Reception, Lawyers' Club, 04/15/1972 (Box 5, Folder 76.7)
    Prof. Parks, Leslie Carter, James Rees
  - Senior Reception, Lawyers' Club, 04/15/1972 (Box 5, Folder 76.8)
    Mike Miskousky, Roseanne Caggiano, William Cinnamond
  - Senior Reception, Lawyers' Club, 04/15/1972 (Box 5, Folder 76.9)
    Mark Weinstein, Mrs. Shoneman, Charles Shoneman, Richard Allen
  - Senior Reception, Lawyers' Club, 04/15/1972 (Box 5, Folder 76.1)
    Mr. and Mrs. Glenn Whitaker
  - Senior Reception, Lawyers' Club, 04/15/1972 (Box 5, Folder 76.11)
    Mrs. Sharpe, Prof. Sharpe, Mrs. Daghtara, Cliff Dougherty, Resa Dashtara
  - Senior Reception, Lawyers' Club, 04/15/1972 (Box 5, Folder 76.12)
    Dennis Kohler, James W. Spensley
  - Senior Reception, Lawyers' Club, 04/15/1972 (Box 5, Folder 76.13)
    Swadesh Kalsi, Dr. Charles Nutting, E. Weintraub
  - Senior Reception, Lawyers' Club, 04/15/1972 (Box 5, Folder 76.14)
    Mrs. Joseph Cook, Prof. Robinson, Joseph T. Cook, Paula Cass, Larry Gebhard
  - Senior Reception, Lawyers' Club, 04/15/1972 (Box 5, Folder 76.15)
    Mrs. John Austin, John A. Austin, Prof. Arnold Reitz, James W. Spensley
  - Senior Reception, Lawyers' Club, 04/15/1972 (Box 5, Folder 76.16)
    Mrs. Bernard Cohen, Prof. Bernard S. Cohen, Claudia Stone, Alfred G. Collins
  - Senior Reception, Lawyers' Club, 04/15/1972 (Box 5, Folder 76.17)
    Mr and Mrs Thomas Condit, Charles A. Marlowe, Helen Roberts, Charles Wendell
  - Senior Reception, Lawyers' Club, 04/15/1972 (Box 5, Folder 76.18)
    Mrs. Dashtara, Prof. Alessandradel Russo, Reza Dashtara, Dean Nash
  - Senior Reception, Lawyers' Club, 04/15/1972 (Box 5, Folder 76.19)
    Mrs. Mallison, Mr. William Mallison, Mrs. Visser, Mr. R.P. Visser
  - Senior Reception, Lawyers' Club, 04/15/1972 (Box 5, Folder 76.2)
    Dean Potts, Gerdolyn Meyers, Lydia Ann Hall, Ismael Meyers
  - 0First Year Law Student Reception, Evening Division, 09/05/1972 (Box 5, Folder 77.1)
    Lesley Alter, Dean Kramer, Pres. Elliot
  - First Year Law Student Breakfast, 09/06/1972 (Box 5, Folder 77.2)
    William Revoir, Dean Kramer, Pres. Elliot
  - First Year Law Student Reception, Evening Division, 09/05/1972 (Box 5, Folder 77.3)
    Suzanne Vaughters, Dean Kramer
  - First Year Law Student Reception, Evening Division, 09/05/1972 (Box 5, Folder 77.4)
    Al Nadel, Robert Kramer
  - First Year Law Student Reception, Evening Division, 09/05/1972 (Box 5, Folder 77.5)
    Clifford A. Doghtery, Steve Sokolic
  - First Year Law Student Reception, Evening Division, 09/05/1972 (Box 5, Folder 77.6)
    Prof. Hugh Bernard, Charlie Harvey
  - First Year Student Breakfast, May Flower Hotel, 09/06/1972 (Box 5, Folder 77.7)
    Birds-eye view
  - First Year Law Student Breakfast, 09/06/1972 (Box 5, Folder 77.8)
    Jim Kutcher, Pres. Elliot, Dean Kirk Patrick
  - First Year Law Student Reception, Evening Division, 09/05/1972 (Box 5, Folder 77.9)
    Pres. Elliot, Mr. and Mrs. Stephen E. Sokolic
  - People talking at a party, undated (Box 5, Folder 78.1)
  - A man, Jerome Dougherty, and a woman at a party, undated (Box 5, Folder 78.2)
  - Three women and a man at a party, undated (Box 5, Folder 78.3)
  - Dean Kramer and two men socializing, undated (Box 5, Folder 78.4)
  - Mrs. Kramer, a man and a women at a party, undated (Box 5, Folder 78.5)
  - Ken Gould, a man and a woman at a party, undated (Box 5, Folder 78.6)
  - Three men and a women at a party, undated (Box 5, Folder 78.7)
  - John A. Hoglund and two women having a conversation, undated (Box 5, Folder 78.8)
  - Kenneth Montero, Kenneth Green at a party, undated (Box 5, Folder 78.9)
  - Two Men having a conversation, undated (Box 5, Folder 78.1)
  - Carol Ross and a man having a conversation, undated (Box 5, Folder 78.11)
  - A man and a woman having a conversation, undated (Box 5, Folder 78.12)
  - Senior Reception, 04/07/1973 (Box 5, Folder 78.13)
    Mr. and Mrs. Pock and a man having a conversation
  - Jeffery Mimick, Lynn Hiner and a man having a conversation, undated (Box 5, Folder 78.14)
  - Senior Reception, 04/07/1973 (Box 5, Folder 78.15)
    Mr. and Mrs. Paul Pascal, Pres. Elliot
  - Senior Reception, 04/07/1973 (Box 5, Folder 78.16)
    Betty Ann Thompson, G. Michael Richards
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion, Class of 1934, 05/10/1974 (Box 5, Folder 79)
    Dr. Jacob Burns, Robert Kramer, Dr. L.H. Elliot
  - GW Law Alumni Luncheon, New York State Bar Meeting, 01/24/1975 (Box 5, Folder 80.1)
    R. Murphy, M. Mermelstien, D. Baird, S. Alpert, J. Burns, D. Cook, W. Bennett, C. Marimaccic, Clifford Dougherty
  - GW Law Alumni Luncheon, New York State Bar Meeting, 01/24/1975 (Box 5, Folder 80.2)
    C. Dougherty, C. Marinaccio, D. Cook, R. Murphy, J. Burns, W. Bennett, M. Mermelstein, S. Alpert
  - GW Law Alumni Luncheon, New York State Bar Meeting, 01/24/1975 (Box 5, Folder 80.3)
  - GW Law Alumni Luncheon, New York State Bar Meeting, 01/24/1975 (Box 5, Folder 80.4)
    C. A. Dougherty, C. Marinaccio, D. Cook, R. Murphy, J. Burns, T. Bennett, M. Mermetstein, S. Alpert
  - GW Law Alumni Luncheon, New York State Bar Meeting, 01/24/1975 (Box 5, Folder 80.5)
    R. Murphy, M. Mermelstein, D. Baird, S. Alpert, J. Burns, D. Cook, W. Bennett, C. Marianaccio, Dr. Burns, C. Dougherty
  - GW Law Alumni Luncheon, New York State Bar Meeting, 01/24/1975 (Box 5, Folder 80.6)
    R. Murphy, M. Mermelstein, D. Baird, S. Alpert, J. Burns, D. Cook, W. Bennett, C. Marinaccio, Dr. Burns, Clifford A. Dougherty
  - GW Law Alumni Luncheon, New York State Bar Meeting, 01/24/1975 (Box 5, Folder 80.7)
    Dr. S. Alpert, Dr. Jacob Burns, and Donald C. Cook, the recipient of the award for distinguished service as National Chairman of GWU Annual Support Fund Program
  - GW Law Alumni Luncheon, New York State Bar Meeting, 01/24/1975 (Box 5, Folder 80.8)
  - GW Law Alumni Luncheon, New York State Bar Meeting, 01/24/1975 (Box 5, Folder 80.9)
    R. Murphy, M. Mermelstein, S. Alpert, J. Burns, D. Cook, C. Marinaccio, D. Burns, C. Douherty [see print]
  - GW Law Alumni Luncheon, New York State Bar Meeting, 01/24/1975 (Box 5, Folder 80.1)
    R. Murphy, M. Mermelstein, S. Alpert, J. Burns, D. Cook, C. Marinaccio, D. Burns, C. Dougherty [see print]
  - Senior Reception, undated (Box 5, Folder 81.1)
    Students, family, and faculty at annual reception
  - Senior Reception, undated (Box 5, Folder 81.2)
    L. Singer, J. Ehrlichand, R. Kramer
  - Senior Reception, undated (Box 5, Folder 81.3)
    Mr. and Mrs. Nutting, Ikesorkislo woman
  - Senior Reception, undated (Box 5, Folder 81.4)
    J.W. Ehrlich, L. Singer and R. Kramer
  - First Year Law Breakfast, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 82.1)
  - First Year Law Breakfast, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 82.2)
  - First Year Law Breakfast, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 82.3)
  - Senior Reception, 04/25/1970 (Box 5, Folder 83.1)
    Associate Dean Ralph Nash and students
  - Senior Reception, 04/25/1970 (Box 5, Folder 83.2)
    Dean Kramer, E. Wheatley, C.A. Dougherty
  - Senior Reception, 04/25/1970 (Box 5, Folder 83.3)
  - Senior Reception, 04/25/1970 (Box 5, Folder 83.4)
  - Senior Reception, 04/25/1970 (Box 5, Folder 83.5)
  - Senior Recption, 04/25/1970 (Box 5, Folder 83.6)
  - Senior Recption, 04/25/1970 (Box 5, Folder 83.7)
  - Senior Recption, 04/25/1970 (Box 5, Folder 83.8)
  - Senior Recption, 04/25/1970 (Box 5, Folder 83.9)
  - First Year Law Student Breakfast, 09/08/1971 (Box 5, Folder 84.1)
    C. Doughtery, Dean Potts, F. Elwood Davis, E.K. Morris and Alexis Panagakos
  - First Year Law Student Breakfast, 09/08/1971 (Box 5, Folder 84.2)
    Pres. Lloyd Elliot, Peggy McAllister, Dean Kramer, Dean Kirkpatrick, Dean Nash
  - Alumni Award Recipients, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 85.1)
    See attached list
  - Presentation of Distinguished Alumni Award to Robert Ash, 12/28/1976 (Box 6, Folder 85.2)
    C. Dougherty; Dean Potts; Mr. Ash; Pres. Elliot
  - Presentation of Distinguished Alumni Award to Robert Ash, 12/28/1976 (Box 6, Folder 85.3)
    Dean Potts; C. Dougherty; Mr. Ash; Pres. Elliot; D. Mooers
  - Presentation of Distinguished Alumni Award to Robert Ash, 12/28/1976 (Box 6, Folder 85.4)
  - Presentation of Distinguished Alumni Award to Robert Ash, 12/28/1976 (Box 6, Folder 85.5)
  - Presentation of Distinguished Alumni Award to Robert Ash, 12/28/1976 (Box 6, Folder 85.6)
  - ABA Meeting, 08/22/1955 --08/25/1955 (Box 6, Folder 86.1)
    Joe Hughes and Weston Vernon, Jr
  - ABA Meeting, 08/22/1955 --08/25/1955 (Box 6, Folder 86.2)
    Joe Hughes, J. Frank Perrin
  - Senior Reception, 03/14/1981 (Box 6, Folder 87.1)
    Pres. Elliot and Roy Hirschorn
  - Senior Reception, 03/14/1981 (Box 6, Folder 87.2)
    Brent Weingardt chatting with Dean Jerome A. Barron
  - Senior Reception, 03/14/1981 (Box 6, Folder 87.3)
    Dean Jerome A. Barron greeting a female recipant
  - Senior Reception, 03/14/1981 (Box 6, Folder 87.4)
  - Dean Robert Kramer, undated (Box 6, Folder 88.1)
  - Dean Robert Kramer, undated (Box 6, Folder 88.2)
  - Dean Robert Kramer, undated (Box 6, Folder 88.3)
  - Dean Robert Kramer, undated (Box 6, Folder 88.4)
  - Dean Robert Kramer, undated (Box 6, Folder 88.5)
  - Dean Kramer and another woman in grauduation gowns, undated (Box 6, Folder 88.6)
  - GWLA Luncheon, Bar Association Chicago, Illinios, 11/02/1979 (Box 6, Folder 89.1)
    Ray Grossman, Dean Jerome A. Barron, Joseph S. Wright, and Eric V. Youngquist
  - GWLA Luncheon, Bar Association Chicago, Illinios, 11/02/1979 (Box 6, Folder 89.2)
  - D.C. Chapter Luncheon, 02/25/1980 (Box 6, Folder 90.1)
    Speakers
  - D.C. Chapter Luncheon, 02/25/1980 (Box 6, Folder 90.2)
    Speakers and particpants
  - GWLA Luncheon, New York Bar Association, Hilton Hotel, 01/25/1985 (Box 6, Folder 91.1)
    Stuart Kaufman, Clifford Doughtery, Dean Jerome Barron, Jacob Burns, and Donald Mooers
  - GWLA Luncheon, New York Bar Association, Hilton Hotel, 01/25/1985 (Box 6, Folder 91.2)
    Speaker
  - GWLA Luncheon, New York Bar Association, Hilton Hotel, 01/25/1985 (Box 6, Folder 91.3)
  - GWLA Luncheon, New York Bar Association, Hilton Hotel, 01/25/1985 (Box 6, Folder 91.4)
    Participants and speaker
  - GWLA Luncheon, New York Bar Association, Hilton Hotel, 01/25/1985 (Box 6, Folder 91.5)
    Cliff Doughtery and another speaker
  - Burns Library Dedication, 10/18/1984 (Box 6, Folder 92.1)
    Dean Jerome A. Barron, Jacob Burns, Chief Justice Warren Burger, and Pres. Elliot
  - Burns Library Dedication, 10/18/1984 (Box 6, Folder 92.2)
    Chief Justice Warren Burger
  - Burns Library Dedication, 10/18/1984 (Box 6, Folder 92.3)
    Three attendees
  - Burns Library dedication, 10/18/1984 (Box 6, Folder 92.4)
    Copies of Contact Prints, see attached list for identification
  - Pres. Elliot, Dean Kramer, and Hon. Oliver GaschPrint, undated (Box 6, Folder 93.1)
  - GWLA Participants Dining, 10/18/1984 (Box 6, Folder 93.2)
  - Hon. Oliver Gasch congradulated by Glen A. Wilk, 10/18/1984 (Box 6, Folder 93.3)
  - Two men with the Law Appriciation Achievement Award, 06/11/1982 (Box 6, Folder 94.1)
  - James C. Caheris with another man displaying his Law Association Achievement Award, 06/11/1982 (Box 6, Folder 94.2)
  - Alexander L. Steva with his Law Association Professional Achievement Award, 06/11/1982 (Box 6, Folder 94.3)
    Chief Clerk, Dean Edward A Potts, and Prof. David B. Weaver
  - Alexander L. Stevas, Clerk, Supreme Court of the United States, 07/1981 (Box 6, Folder 94.4)
  - Van Vleck Moot Court Case Club Dinner, 02/21/1981 (Box 6, Folder 96.1)
    1981 Upper Class Winners and Judges[see print for identification]
  - Van Vleck Moot Court Case Club Dinner, 02/21/1981 (Box 6, Folder 96.2)
  - Van Vleck Moot Court Case Club Dinner, 02/21/1981 (Box 6, Folder 96.3)
  - Van Vleck Moot Court Case Club, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 96.4)
    Dean Jerome A. Barron presents the prize moneychecks to the 1980-81 upperclass winners of the Van Vleck Moot Court to William P. Tedesco and Sally Ann Hostetler
  - Van Vleck Moot Court Case Club, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 96.5)
  - Van Vleck Moot Court Case Club Dinner, 02/21/1981 (Box 6, Folder 96.6)
  - Van Vleck Moot Court Case Club, 02/27/1982 (Box 6, Folder 96.7)
    Judge Oliver Gasch, Sally Hostetler, and William Paul Tedesco
  - Van Vleck Moot Court Case Club, 02/27/1982 (Box 6, Folder 96.8)
  - Van Vleck Moot Court Case Club, 02/25/1984 (Box 6, Folder 96.9)
    Clifford Dougherty presents awards to Katheryn Rogers and Mary Qualiana
  - Van Vleck Moot Court Case Club, 02/25/1984 (Box 6, Folder 96.1)
  - Van Vleck Moot Court Case Club, 02/25/1984 (Box 6, Folder 96.11)
    Dean Jerome Barron presents award to Samuel R. Maizel
  - Van Vleck Moot Court Case Club, 02/25/1984 (Box 6, Folder 96.12)
  - Van Vleck Moot Court Case Club, 02/25/1984 (Box 6, Folder 96.13)
  - Van Vleck Moot Court Case Club, 02/23/1985 (Box 6, Folder 96.14)
    Dean Jerome Barron presents award to James R. Simms III
  - Van Vleck Moot Court Case Club, 02/23/1985 (Box 6, Folder 96.15)
  - Van Vleck Moot Court Case Club, 02/22/1986 (Box 6, Folder 96.16)
    Dean Jerome Barron presents awards to Robert W. Muilenburg and Steven R. Becker
  - Van Vleck Moot Court Case Club, 02/22/1986 (Box 6, Folder 96.17)
  - Van Vleck Moot Court Case Club, 02/14/1987 (Box 6, Folder 96.18)
    Dean Jerome Barron presents awards to Micheal A. Nemeroff and Peter D. Russin
  - Van Vleck Moot Court Case Club, 02/14/1987 (Box 6, Folder 96.19)
  - Van Vleck Moot Court Case Club, 02/14/1987 (Box 6, Folder 96.2)
  - Van Vleck Moot Court Case Club, 02/13/1988 (Box 6, Folder 96.21)
    Dean Jerome Barron presents awards to Steven R. Horne and Denise M. Jennings
  - Van Vleck Moot Court Case Club, 02/13/1988 (Box 6, Folder 96.22)
  - Van Vleck Moot Court Case Club, 02/13/1988 (Box 6, Folder 96.23)
  - Katherine Daniels, JD '86, undated (Box 6, Folder 97.1)
  - Stan C. Kaiman, '64Print, undated (Box 6, Folder 97.2)
  - Thomas E. Graham, JD '84, 10/1987 (Box 6, Folder 97.3)
  - Renato Guimaraes Jr, undated (Box 6, Folder 97.4)
  - Fronces Francis, undated (Box 6, Folder 97.5)
  - Michaelle Nardozzi, undated (Box 6, Folder 97.6)
    Chevron Scholarship Recipient
  - J. Frank Perrin, undated (Box 6, Folder 97.7)
  - William J. Driver, LLB '52, undated (Box 6, Folder 97.8)
  - Joseph A. DeGrandi, LLB '61, undated (Box 6, Folder 97.9)
  - Ruth Timberlobe Prohop JD '61, undated (Box 6, Folder 97.1)
  - Marion Edwyn Harrison, undated (Box 6, Folder 97.11)
  - Joseph Kalef '85, undated (Box 6, Folder 97.12)
  - Philip R. Arvidson, JD '65, undated (Box 6, Folder 97.13)
  - Betty Ann Thompson, LLB "48 Pres. GWLA, 09/12/1979 (Box 6, Folder 97.14)
  - G. Clay Smith Jr., LLM '70, SJD '77, 09/10/1981 (Box 6, Folder 97.15)
  - John S. Jenkins, undated (Box 6, Folder 97.16)
  - Stephen Spivack, JD '72, undated (Box 6, Folder 97.17)
  - Jean S. Fugett, Jr., undated (Box 6, Folder 97.18)
  - Dean Jack Friedenthal, undated (Box 6, Folder 97.19)
  - Hugh Don Campbell, undated (Box 6, Folder 97.2)
  - Robert D. Krumme, Vice Pres. and general counsal, undated (Box 6, Folder 97.21)
  - Richard B. Abell, JD '74, Assistant Attorney, undated (Box 6, Folder 97.22)
  - Francis W. Campbell, '51, undated (Box 6, Folder 97.23)
  - Philip M. Howe, JD '70, undated (Box 6, Folder 97.24)
  - Dennis S. Kahane, '72, undated (Box 6, Folder 97.25)
  - Dante Cancelli, LLM '81, undated (Box 6, Folder 97.26)
  - H. Richard Mayberry, undated (Box 6, Folder 97.27)
  - Ron Jessamy, '73, undated (Box 6, Folder 97.28)
  - Don Schellhardt, undated (Box 6, Folder 97.29)
  - George M. Knapp, 02/12/1988 (Box 6, Folder 97.3)
  - Robert P. Voyles, LLM 83', undated (Box 6, Folder 97.31)
  - Clifford A. Doughtery, undated (Box 6, Folder 97.32)
  - Pres. Elliot Addressing paticipants, undated (Box 6, Folder 97.33)
  - Pres. Elliot Addressing paticipants, undated (Box 6, Folder 97.34)
  - Judge Lawerence S. Margolis, JD 61, undated (Box 6, Folder 97.35)
  - T. Hiatt, JD '67, undated (Box 6, Folder 97.36)
  - A man, undated (Box 6, Folder 97.38)
  - A woman, undated (Box 6, Folder 97.39)
  - Dean Jerome Barron, undated (Box 6, Folder 98.1)
    Television still
  - Dean Jerome Barron with an award recepient, undated (Box 6, Folder 98.2)
  - Dean Jerome Barron with an award recepient, undated (Box 6, Folder 98.3)
  - Dean Jerome Barron with an award recepient, undated (Box 6, Folder 98.4)
  - GWLA meeting, undated (Box 6, Folder 98.5)
    Pres. Elliot, Dean Barron, and other participants chatting
  - Dean Jerome Barron with a group of patricipants and an award winner, undated (Box 6, Folder 98.6)
  - American Bar Association Meeting, undated (Box 6, Folder 98.7)
    Dean Barron, John O. Graybeal and others
  - Pres. Elliot, Jacob Burns, and Dean Robert Kramer, undated (Box 6, Folder 99.1)
  - Pre. Elliot presents an award to Jacob Burns, undated (Box 6, Folder 99.2)
  - GWLA Luncheon, New York Bar Association Meeting, 01/23/1981 (Box 6, Folder 99.3)
    Pres. Elliot presents an award to John R. Stafford, LLB 62'
  - Pres. Elliot and others in graduation gowns, undated (Box 6, Folder 99.4)
  - Pres. Elliot with Richard N, Nelson, Kenneth Kraft and a female student, undated (Box 6, Folder 99.5)
  - Pres. Elliot, John Pierucki, Guy Doo Hoo, James E. Goodwin, undated (Box 6, Folder 99.6)
  - Lines, Baca, Franklin, Kramer, Charles Salmon, Jack A. Smith, Harry S. Fich, undated (Box 6, Folder 99.7)
  - Charles Salmon, Jack A. Smith, Harry S. Fich, Dean Kramer, Lines, Baca, Franklin, undated (Box 6, Folder 99.8)
  - General Alumni Mtg. San Francisco, undated (Box 6, Folder 99.9)
    Dave Brown, Dean Kramer, Sutton John P., Pres. Elliot
  - General Alumni Mtg. Raleigh, North Carolina, undated (Box 6, Folder 99.1)
    Amistead T. Mauping JD '40, Pres. Elliot, Robert C. Savage, Law ,26
  - Alumni Leadership in San Francis, 01/1973 (Box 6, Folder 99.11)
    Da Angelo M. May MD '37,Thomas F. Smegal, JD'31, Pres. Elliot, Franis R. Kirkham JD '31, and Judge Frank E. Hart JD '53
  - Academic Center, undated (Oversize-folder 6)
    Oversize
  - The GWU law School Buidling, undated (Box 6, Folder 102.1)
  - The GWU law School Buidling, undated (Box 6, Folder 102.2)
  - The GWU law School Buidling, undated (Box 6, Folder 102.3)
  - The GWU law School Buidling, undated (Box 6, Folder 102.4)
  - Memorial Luncheon for Josheph B. Danzansky JD '36, 05/14/1982 (Box 6, Folder 103.1)
    Stephen I. Dazansky, JD '64 speaking in memory of his late father
  - D.C. Chapter, Law Alumni Association Luncheon, undated (Box 6, Folder 103.2)
    Congressman Michael D. Barnes, JD '72 addresses audience
  - "Oral History" Luncheon Series, undated (Box 6, Folder 103.3)
    Judge Joyce Hens Green is interviewed by Jacob A. Stein, Pres. D.C. Chapter
  - Jack Fey Dinner, 11/10/1981 (Box 6, Folder 103.4)
    Pres. Elliot and three other men
  - GW Law Alumni Luncheon, Conn. Bar, 05/06/1982 (Box 6, Folder 103.5)
    Maurice R. Gersten, Dean Jerome Barron, Judge Richard C. Noreu, Judge Joane K. Kulawiz
  - GW Law Alumni Luncheon, Boise, Idaho, 09/14/1981 (Box 6, Folder 103.6)
    Robert M. Taylor, H. Fred Kennedy, Ron J. Twilegar, Robert M. Taylor Jr, John R. Rowe, Patria R. Gallagner, Edith Miller Klein, Hon Robert E. Smylie
  - GW Law Alumni Dinner, Cleveland, Ohio, undated (Box 6, Folder 103.7)
    Associate Dean Edward A Potts, with Fred J. Deuber, Elaine R. Crane, Jack M. Young, William Tabac
  - GW Law Alumni Dinner, Cleveland, Ohio, undated (Box 6, Folder 103.8)
    John H (Bert) Mulholland, Hon. Hal D. Cooper, Donald A. Rowe, Richard H. Childress, Charles M. Rosenberg
  - Dockside party for GW Law Alumni, MD Bar Ass. Meeting, 06/11/1982 (Box 6, Folder 104.1)
    Ronald Willoner hosted the party on his boat "Serendipity"
  - Virginia State Bar, Annual Meeting in VA Beach, 06/16/1984 (Box 6, Folder 104.2)
  - Florida Bar Convention, Disney World, 06/16/1979 (Box 6, Folder 104.3)
    Robert W. Wudworth, LLB '62
  - GW Law Alumni Luncheon, Kansas State Bar, 05/15/1978 (Box 6, Folder 104.4)
    Arthur C. Hodgson, Janet M. Jonas, Carlos F. Lucero, Mrs. Lucero, Carten C. Johannsen
  - GW Law Alumni Breakfast, Texas State Bar, San Antonio, 06/29/1979 (Box 6, Folder 104.5)
    Dean Jerome A. Barron, Charles W. Hanor, Thomas Garza
  - Chicago University Club, 03/5/1979 (Box 6, Folder 104.6)
    George H. Gerstmor, Jesse M. Moore, Joseph Wright Jr., James P. Hume
  - New Jersey Bar, 05/18/1973 (Box 6, Folder 104.7)
    Arthur Jacob, Edwood Davis, Gerlald Gorrin, Charles Landesman
  - Washington State Bar, 09/18/1981 (Box 6, Folder 104.8)
    Chemrich, Zabel; Broz, Garrett; and Sherwood
  - Law Alumni Luncheon, Las Vegas, Nevada, 07/10/1973 (Box 6, Folder 105.1)
    Participants at a luncheon, Union Plaza Hotel
  - Law Alumni Luncheon, Las Vegas, Nevada, 07/10/1973 (Box 6, Folder 105.2)
  - Law Alumni Luncheon, Las Vegas, Nevada, 07/10/1973 (Box 6, Folder 105.3)
  - Law Alumni Luncheon, Las Vegas, Nevada, 07/10/1973 (Box 6, Folder 105.4)
    Sen. Le E. Walker, Eleanor Davis, Peter Burleigh, F. Elwood Davis
  - Law Alumni Luncheon, Las Vegas, Nevada, 07/10/1973 (Box 6, Folder 105.5)
    Participants chatting at the Union Plaza Hotel
  - Law Alumni Luncheon, Las Vegas, Nevada, 07/10/1973 (Box 6, Folder 105.6)
  - Law Alumni Luncheon, Las Vegas, Nevada, 07/10/1973 (Box 6, Folder 105.7)
  - Law Alumni Luncheon, Las Vegas, Nevada, 07/10/1973 (Box 6, Folder 105.8)
  - Liner, Baca, Gase, undated (Box 6, Folder 106.1)
  - Mrs. Casaust, Franklin and another man, undated (Box 6, Folder 106.2)
  - Pres Elliot and Mr. and Mrs Grammer, undated (Box 6, Folder 106.3)
  - Participants with refreshments, undated (Box 6, Folder 106.4)
  - A woman, undated (Box 6, Folder 106.5)
  - [l. - r.]Dan Tingey, Mike Sloan, Harry Reid, Don Davidson, Jerry Seiler, Charles Johnson, Marion Earl, Rulon Earl, undated (Box 6, Folder 106.6)
  - Four men participants, undated (Box 6, Folder 106.7)
  - Participants, undated (Box 6, Folder 106.8)
  - A participant with his award, undated (Box 6, Folder 106.9)
  - Cliff Dougherty receiving an award, undated (Box 6, Folder 106.1)
  - Participants chatting, undated (Box 6, Folder 106.11)
  - Pres. Elliot with two of the participants, undated (Box 6, Folder 106.12)
  - Three participants in front of the Judicial Bldg, undated (Box 6, Folder 106.13)
  - Participants with thier awards, undated (Box 6, Folder 106.14)
  - Negatives for prints of folder #106, undated (Box 6, Folder 106.15)
  - Negatives for prints of folder #106, undated (Box 6, Folder 106.16)
  - Pres. Elliot with two male participants, undated (Box 6, Folder 107.1)
  - GWLA Breakfast, Texas Bar Association, 07/10/1984 (Box 6, Folder 107.2)
  - President's Reception, Reunion Weekend, 06/1987 (Box 6, Folder 107.3)
  - Participants dinning, 02/1986 (Box 6, Folder 107.4)
  - An individual and a group photos, undated (Box 6, Folder 107.5)
  - A group photo of participants in the Law School, undated (Box 6, Folder 107.6)
  - A group photo of participants, 02/1986 (Box 6, Folder 107.7)
  - Participants chatting over refreshments, 02/1986 (Box 6, Folder 107.8)
  - A participant receives his award, undated (Box 6, Folder 107.9)
  - Participants chatting, undated (Box 6, Folder 107.1)
  - Copy of contact print, undated (Box 6, Folder 107.11)
  - Copy of Contact print of an individual, undated (Box 6, Folder 107.12)
  - An article on W. C. Spangle, 02/28/1976 (Box 6, Folder 107.13)
  - Invitation card for the Cocktail at Minneapolis Club, undated (Box 6, Folder 107.14)
    GWLA Alumni Event
  - Alumni address cards, undated (Box 6, Folder 107.15)